Guide to the Allegheny County, Pa. Coroner's Office Records, 1884-1976 AIS.1982.07
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Allegheny County, Pa. Coroner's Office Records
1884-1976
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Allegheny County (Pa.). Coroner's Office
AIS.1982.07
1087.5 Linear Feet (870 boxes)
The Coroner's Office investigates suspicious, unusual and sudden deaths in Allegheny County, Pennsylvania. These records contain inquest files dating between 1887 and 1976, which reflect coroner's verdicts for over ninety years. In addition to the final inquest report, materials in the files may include eye-witness testimony, grand jury reports, physician notes, affidavits, press clippings and other documentation. Also included in these records are morgue reports covering intermittent years from 1901 to 1941, along with a small amount of administrative files. Digital reproductions of some of the notable case files are scanned and online.
History
The Office of the Coroner for Allegheny County, Pennsylvania, has developed into one of the leading medico-legal programs in the country. Historically, the title of coroner could be held by any land owning citizen, with professions ranging from a cabinet maker, to a silver smith, farmer, or lawyer, but seldom were they physicians. Until recently, the coroner had jurisdiction over crimes such as robbery, rape and burglary, in addition to homicides. As late as the early nineteenth century, the Pennsylvania Supreme Court ruled that these common law powers still inherently rested with the coroner. In 1972, the coroner statutes became codified and those seldom-used common law powers of the coroner were officially abolished.
By the turn of the century, the Coroner's Office in Allegheny County was well on its way to becoming a fully developed medico-legal investigative agency. Employees took an active role in performing autopsies, rather than hiring private physicians to do the work. In 1965, Allegheny County voters elected their first physician as coroner, Dr. William Hunt. Since that time, the office has made its professional expertise available upon request to Coroners' Offices and law enforcement agencies in surrounding counties.
Scope and Content Notes
These records contain information about the causes of death in Allegheny County, Pennsylvania, from 1884 to 1973, along with other legal information from the Coroner's offices through 1976. There are three series: Coroner inquests files, morgue reports, and administrative records. For the individual scope and content notes, please see below.
The Coroner Inquest files date from 1887 to 1973. They are public records open to all, as affirmed by the Allegheny County Coroner's Office. The records were created by the Coroner's Office to satisfy public law. In addition to the final inquest report, materials in the files may include eye-witness testimony, grand jury reports, physician notes, affidavits, press clippings and other documentation. Ephemeral material such as photographs, tissue samples, bullets, suicide notes, and other items have been retained with the original files. There is a five year gap in the records between 1933 and 1938; these records are not present.
These records also contain morgue reports from the Allegheny County Coroner's Office. The responsibilities of the Coroner include transporting and disposing of bodies, investigating causes and manner of deaths, and determining whether an autopsy is needed. The morgue reports allowed for record keeping of arrivals, transfers and releases of the bodies to funeral homes. See below for more detail of the files.
A small amount of administrative records include case files that are undated, correspondence, minutes from meetings, and other records from the Coroner's Office.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
In 1982, the Coroner's Office of Allegheny County transferred and deposited inquest case records, morgue reports, and administrative records from 1884 to 1976, to the University of Pittsburgh.
Previous Citation
Allegheny County, Pa. Coroner's Office Records, 1884-1976, AIS.1982.07, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Judicial records; Coroners -- Pennsylvania -- Allegheny County -- Records and correspondence; Death -- Pennsylvania -- Allegheny County -- Causes; Government; Morgues -- Pennsylvania -- Allegheny County -- Records and correspondence; Allegheny County (Pa.); Allegheny County (Pa.). Coroner's Office
- Coroner Case Files, I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  The records are arranged by docket number, which were numbered in order by the date the case was filed by the Office of the Coroner. Please note that date of death and date of inquest may be months and in some cases years apart. The Archives Service Center has created a separate name and date index available electronically which can be searched on site to help patrons identify material. Please contact the Archives Service Center for more information about this service.
  - Coroner Case Files, 1887-1973; 1.
    - Docket Range 188701-001 through 188706-327 (Box 1)
    - Docket Range 188706-328 through 188711-160 (Box 2)
    - Docket Range 188711-160 through 188804-425 (Box 3)
    - Docket Range 188804-426 through 188808-200 (Box 4)
    - Docket Range 188808-201 through 188903-115 (Box 5)
    - Docket Range 188903-116 through 188909-043 (Box 6)
    - Docket Range 188910-044 through 189002-350 (Box 7)
    - Docket Range 189003-351 through 189006-160 (Box 8)
    - Docket Range 189006-161 through 189010-013 (Box 9)
    - Docket Range 189010-014 through 189012-249 (Box 10)
    - Docket Range 189101-250 through 189105-100 (Box 11)
    - Docket Range 189106-101 through 189109-332 (Box 12)
    - Docket Range 189109-333 through 189112-119 (Box 13)
    - Docket Range 189201-120 through 189204-318 (Box 14)
    - Docket Range 189204-319 through 189207-114 (Box 15)
    - Docket Range 189207-115 through 189210-388 (Box 16)
    - Docket Range 189210-389 through 189301-116 (Box 17)
    - Docket Range 189301-117 through 189305-347 (Box 18)
    - Docket Range 189305-348 through 189308-135 (Box 19)
    - Docket Range 189308-136 through 189312-386 (Box 20)
    - Docket Range 189312-387 through 189403-117 (Box 21)
    - Docket Range 189403-118 through 189407-388 (Box 22)
    - Docket Range 189407-389 through 189410-150 (Box 23)
    - Docket Range 189410-151 through 189503-450 (Box 24)
    - Docket Range 189503-451 through 189506-247 (Box 25)
    - Docket Range 189506-248 through 189509-052 (Box 26)
    - Docket Range 189509-053 through 189512-292 (Box 27)
    - Docket Range 189512-293 through 189604-063 (Box 28)
    - Docket Range 189604-064 through 189607-313 (Box 29)
    - Docket Range 189607-314 through 189610-073 (Box 30)
    - Docket Range 189610-073 through 189702-365 (Box 31)
    - Docket Range 189702-366 through 189706-159 (Box 32)
    - Docket Range 189706-160 through 189709-464 (Box 33)
    - Docket Range 189709-465 through 189801-285 (Box 34)
    - Docket Range 189801-286 through 189805-063 (Box 35)
    - Docket Range 189805-064 through 189807-373 (Box 36)
    - Docket Range 189808-374 through 189810-130 (Box 37)
    - Docket Range 189810-131 through 189901-80 (Box 38)
    - Docket Range 189901-081 through 189904-353 (Box 39)
    - Docket Range 189904-354 through 189906-099 (Box 40)
    - Docket Range 189906-100 through 189908-312 (Box 41)
    - Docket Range 189908-313 through 189910-495 (Box 42)
    - Docket Range 189910-496 through 189911-150 (Box 43)
    - Docket Range 189911-151 through 189912-273 (Box 44)
    - Docket Range 189912-274 through 190001-354 (Box 45)
    - Docket Range 190001-355 through 190001-449 (Box 46)
    - Docket Range 190001-450 through 190002-31 (Box 47)
    - Docket Range 190002-32 through 190002-97 (Box 48)
    - Docket Range 190003-98 through 190003-157 (Box 49)
    - Docket Range 190003-158 through 190003-209 (Box 50)
    - Docket Range 190003-210 through 190004-300 (Box 51)
    - Docket Range 190004-301 through 190005-380 (Box 52)
    - Docket Range 190005-381 through 190005-448 (Box 53)
    - Docket Range 190005-449 through 190006-71 (Box 54)
    - Docket Range 190006-72 through 190006-183 (Box 55)
    - Docket Range 190007-192 through 190007-270 (Box 56)
    - Docket Range 190007-271 through 190008-370 (Box 57)
    - Docket Range 190008-371 through 190008-476 (Box 58)
    - Docket Range 190008-477 through 190010-80 (Box 59)
    - Docket Range 190010-81 through 190011-188 (Box 60)
    - Docket Range 190011-189 through 190012-321 (Box 61)
    - Docket Range 190012-322 through 190012-425 (Box 62)
    - Docket Range 190012-426 through 190101-29 (Box 63)
    - Docket Range 190101-30 through 190102-156 (Box 64)
    - Docket Range 190102-157 through 190103-270 (Box 65)
    - Docket Range 190103-271 through 190103-361 (Box 66)
    - Docket Range 190103-362 through 190104-468 (Box 67)
    - Docket Range 190104-469 through 190105-105 (Box 68)
    - Docket Range 190105-106 through 190106-26 (Box 69)
    - Docket Range 190106-27 through 190107-442 (Box 70)
    - Docket Range 190107-443 through 190108-98 (Box 71)
    - Docket Range 190108-99 through 190109-274 (Box 72)
    - Docket Range 190109-275 through 190110-446 (Box 73)
    - Docket Range 190110-447 through 190111-79 (Box 74)
    - Docket Range 190111-80 through 190112-229 (Box 75)
    - Docket Range 190112-230 through 190201-28 (Box 76)
    - Docket Range 190201-29 through 190201-214 (Box 77)
    - Docket Range 190201-215 through 190203-406 (Box 78)
    - Docket Range 190203-407 through 190204-28 (Box 79)
    - Docket Range 190204-29 through 190205-207 (Box 80)
    - Docket Range 190205-208 through 190206-408 (Box 81)
    - Docket Range 190206-409 through 190207-78 (Box 82)
    - Docket Range 190207-79 through 190207-246 (Box 83)
    - Docket Range 190207-247 through 190208-366 (Box 84)
    - Docket Range 190208-367 through 190209-11 (Box 85)
    - Docket Range 190209-12 through 190210-199 (Box 86)
    - Docket Range 190210-200 through 190211-405 (Box 87)
    - Docket Range 190211-406 through 190212-91 (Box 88)
    - Docket Range 190212-92 through 190301-376 (Box 89)
    - Docket Range 190301-377 through 190302-59 (Box 90)
    - Docket Range 190302-60 through 190303-205 (Box 91)
    - Docket Range 190303-206 through 190304-353 (Box 92)
    - Docket Range 190304-354 through 190305-12 (Box 93)
    - Docket Range 190305-13 through 190306-195 (Box 94)
    - Docket Range 190306-196 through 190307-403 (Box 95)
    - Docket Range 190307-404 through 190308-194 (Box 96)
    - Docket Range 190308-195 through 190309-376 (Box 97)
    - Docket Range 190309-377 through 190310-25 (Box 98)
    - Docket Range 190310-26 through 190311-200 (Box 99)
    - Docket Range 190311-201 through 190312-442 (Box 100)
    - Docket Range 190312-443 through 190402-229 (Box 101)
    - Docket Range 190402-230 through 190403-429 (Box 102)
    - Docket Range 190403-430 through 190404-109 (Box 103)
    - Docket Range 190404-110 through 190404-366 (Box 104)
    - Docket Range 190404-367 through 190405-49 (Box 105)
    - Docket Range 190405-50 through 190406-214 (Box 106)
    - Docket Range 190406-215 through 190407-431 (Box 107)
    - Docket Range 190407-432 through 190408-155 (Box 108)
    - Docket Range 190408-156 through 190410-360 (Box 109)
    - Docket Range 190410-361 through 190411-93 (Box 110)
    - Docket Range 190411-94 through 190501-352 (Box 111)
    - Docket Range 190412-353 through 190502-176 (Box 112)
    - Docket Range 190502-177 through 190503-353 (Box 113)
    - Docket Range 190503-354 through 190503-469 (Box 114)
    - Docket Range 190503-70 through 190504-88 (Box 115)
    - Docket Range 190504-89 through 190505-219 (Box 116)
    - Docket Range 190505-220 through 190506-376 (Box 117)
    - Docket Range 190506-377 through 190507-65 (Box 118)
    - Docket Range 190507-66 through 190508-234 (Box 119)
    - Docket Range 190508-235 through 190508-387 (Box 120)
    - Docket Range 190508-388 through 190509-33 (Box 121)
    - Docket Range 190509-34 through 190510-205 (Box 122)
    - Docket Range 190510-206 through 190511-400 (Box 123)
    - Docket Range 19051-401 through 190601-10 (Box 124)
    - Docket Range 190601-11 through 190601-173 (Box 125)
    - Docket Range 190601-174 through 190602-119 (Box 126)
    - Docket Range 190602-120 through 190603-117 (Box 127)
    - Docket Range 190603-118 through 190604-90 (Box 128)
    - Docket Range 190604-91 through 190605-71 (Box 129)
    - Docket Range 190605-72 through 190606-92 (Box 130)
    - Docket Range 190606-93 through 190607-39 (Box 131)
    - Docket Range 190607-40 through 190607-214 (Box 132)
    - Docket Range 190607-215 through 190608-196 (Box 133)
    - Docket Range 190608-197 through 190609-162 (Box 134)
    - Docket Range 190609-163 through 190610-162 (Box 135)
    - Docket Range 190610-163 through 190611-77 (Box 136)
    - Docket Range 190611-78 through 190612-74 (Box 137)
    - Docket Range 190612-75 through 190701-55 (Box 138)
    - Docket Range 190701-56 through 190702-50 (Box 139)
    - Docket Range 190702-51 through 190703-49 (Box 140)
    - Docket Range 190703-50 through 190704-75 (Box 141)
    - Docket Range 190704-76 through 190705-26 (Box 142)
    - Docket Range 190705-27 through 109706-51 (Box 143)
    - Docket Range 190706-52 through 109707-34 (Box 144)
    - Docket Range 109707-35 through 109708-07 (Box 145)
    - Docket Range 109708-08 through 190708-215 (Box 146)
    - Docket Range 190708-216 through 109709-211 (Box 147)
    - Docket Range 109709-212 through 190710-206 (Box 148)
    - Docket Range 190710-207 through 190711-189 (Box 149)
    - Docket Range 190711-190 through 190712-199 (Box 150)
    - Docket Range 190712-200 through 190801-169 (Box 151)
    - Docket Range 190801-170 through 190802-200 (Box 152)
    - Docket Range 190802-201 through 190804-124 (Box 153)
    - Docket Range 190804-125 through 190806-32 (Box 154)
    - Docket Range 190806-33 through 190807-75 (Box 155)
    - Docket Range 190806-76 through 90808-147 (Box 156)
    - Docket Range 190808-148 through 190810-24 (Box 157)
    - Docket Range 190810-25 through 190811-69 (Box 158)
    - Docket Range 190811-70 through 190812-124 (Box 159)
    - Docket Range 190812-125 through 190901-123 (Box 160)
    - Docket Range 190901-124 through 190903-37 (Box 161)
    - Docket Range 190903-38 through 190904-52 (Box 162)
    - Docket Range 190904-53 through 190905-73 (Box 163)
    - Docket Range 190905-74 through 190906-40 (Box 164)
    - Docket Range 190906-41 through 190907-18 (Box 165)
    - Docket Range 190906-19 through 190907-208 (Box 166)
    - Docket Range 190907-209 through 190908-167 (Box 167)
    - Docket Range 190908-168 through 190909-185 (Box 168)
    - Docket Range 190909-186 through 190911-42 (Box 169)
    - Docket Range 190911-43 through 190912-67 (Box 170)
    - Docket Range 190912-68 through 191001-66 (Box 171)
    - Docket Range 191001-67 through 191002-26 (Box 172)
    - Docket Range 191002-27 through 191003-38 (Box 173)
    - Docket Range 191003-39 through 191003-248 (Box 174)
    - Docket Range 191003-249 through 191004-222 (Box 175)
    - Docket Range 191004-223 through 191005-186 (Box 176)
    - Docket Range 191005-187 through 191006-198 (Box 177)
    - Docket Range 191006-199 through 191007-206 (Box 178)
    - Docket Range 191007-207 through 191008-173 (Box 179)
    - Docket Range 191008-174 through 191009-129 (Box 180)
    - Docket Range 191009-130 through 191010-67 (Box 181)
    - Docket Range 191010-68 through 191011-17 (Box 182)
    - Docket Range 191011-18 through 191011-182 (Box 183)
    - Docket Range 191011-183 through 191012-184 (Box 184)
    - Docket Range 191012-185 through 191101-112 (Box 185)
    - Docket Range 191101-113 through 191102-66 (Box 186)
    - Docket Range 191102-67 through 191103-53 (Box 187)
    - Docket Range 191103-54 through 191104-41 (Box 188)
    - Docket Range 191104-42 through 191105-41 (Box 189)
    - Docket Range 191105-42 through 191106-34 (Box 190)
    - Docket Range 191106-35 through 191106-206 (Box 191)
    - Docket Range 191106-207 through 191107-153 (Box 192)
    - Docket Range 191107-154 through 191108-41 (Box 193)
    - Docket Range 191108-42 through 191109-19 (Box 194)
    - Docket Range 191109-20 through 191110-19 (Box 195)
    - Docket Range 191110-20 through 191110-118 (Box 196)
    - Docket Range 191110-189 through 191111-197 (Box 197)
    - Docket Range 191111-198 through 191112-157 (Box 198)
    - Docket Range 191112-158 through 191201-152 (Box 199)
    - Docket Range 191201-153 through 191202-93 (Box 200)
    - Docket Range 191202-94 through 191203-58 (Box 201)
    - Docket Range 191203-59 through 191203-247 (Box 202)
    - Docket Range 191203-248 through 191204-178 (Box 203)
    - Docket Range 191204-179 through 191205-161 (Box 204)
    - Docket Range 191205-162 through 191206-151 (Box 205)
    - Docket Range 191206-152 through 191207-163 (Box 206)
    - Docket Range 191207-164 through 191208-122 (Box 207)
    - Docket Range 191208-123 through 191209-111 (Box 208)
    - Docket Range 191209-112 through 191210-101 (Box 209)
    - Docket Range 191210-102 through 191211-9 (Box 210)
    - Docket Range 191211-10 through 191211-179 (Box 211)
    - Docket Range 191211-180 through 191212-148 (Box 212)
    - Docket Range 191212-149 through 191301-98 (Box 213)
    - Docket Range 191301-99 through 191302-16 (Box 214)
    - Docket Range 191302-17 through 191302-239 (Box 215)
    - Docket Range 191302-240 through 191303-231 (Box 216)
    - Docket Range 191303-232 through 191304-194 (Box 217)
    - Docket Range 191304-195 through 191305-156 (Box 218)
    - Docket Range 191305-157 through 191306-93 (Box 219)
    - Docket Range 191306-94 through 191307-28 (Box 220)
    - Docket Range 191307-29 through 191307-263 (Box 221)
    - Docket Range 191307-264 through 191308-209 (Box 222)
    - Docket Range 191308-210 through 191309-166 (Box 223)
    - Docket Range 191309-167 through 191310-124 (Box 224)
    - Docket Range 191310-125 through 191311-52 (Box 225)
    - Docket Range 191311-53 through 191312-26 (Box 226)
    - Docket Range 191312-27 through 191312-226 (Box 227)
    - Docket Range 191312-227 through 191401-176 (Box 228)
    - Docket Range 191401-177 through 191402-78 (Box 229)
    - Docket Range 191402-79 through 191403-80 (Box 230)
    - Docket Range 191403-81 through 191404-7 (Box 231)
    - Docket Range 191404-8 through 191404-186 (Box 232)
    - Docket Range 191404-187 through 191405-146 (Box 233)
    - Docket Range 191405-147 through 191406-135 (Box 234)
    - Docket Range 191406-136 through 191407-62 (Box 235)
    - Docket Range 191407-63 through 191408-57 (Box 236)
    - Docket Range 191408-58 through 191409-90 (Box 237)
    - Docket Range 191409-91 through 191410-78 (Box 238)
    - Docket Range 191410-79 through 191411-79 (Box 239)
    - Docket Range 191411-80 through 191412-32 (Box 240)
    - Docket Range 191412-33 through 191412-239 (Box 241)
    - Docket Range 191412-240 through 191502-26 (Box 242)
    - Docket Range 191502-27 through 191503-83 (Box 243)
    - Docket Range 191503-84 through 191504-47 (Box 244)
    - Docket Range 191504-48 through 191505-64 (Box 246)
    - Docket Range 191505-65 through 191506-75 (Box 246)
    - Docket Range 191506-76 through 191507-99 (Box 247)
    - Docket Range 191507-100 through 191508-88 (Box 248)
    - Docket Range 191508-89 through 191509-150 (Box 249)
    - Docket Range 191509-151 through 191510-196 (Box 250)
    - Docket Range 191510-197 through 191511-150 (Box 251)
    - Docket Range 191511-151 through 191512-202 (Box 252)
    - Docket Range 191512-203 through 191601-177 (Box 253)
    - Docket Range 191601-178 through 191602-87 (Box 254)
    - Docket Range 191602-88 through 191603-86 (Box 255)
    - Docket Range 191603-87 through 191604-75 (Box 256)
    - Docket Range 191604-76 through 191605-41 (Box 257)
    - Docket Range 191605-42 through 191606-8 (Box 258)
    - Docket Range 191606-9 through 191606-229 (Box 259)
    - Docket Range 191606-230 through 191607-189 (Box 260)
    - Docket Range 191607-190 through 191608-190 (Box 261)
    - Docket Range 191608-191 through 191609-128 (Box 262)
    - Docket Range 191609-129 through 191610-132 (Box 263)
    - Docket Range 191610-133 through 191611-116 (Box 264)
    - Docket Range 191611-117 through 191612-120 (Box 265)
    - Docket Range 191612-121 through 191701-93 (Box 266)
    - Docket Range 191701-94 through 191702-46 (Box 267)
    - Docket Range 191702-47 through 191702-298 (Box 268)
    - Docket Range 191702-299 through 191703-229 (Box 269)
    - Docket Range 191703-230 through 191704-148 (Box 270)
    - Docket Range 191704-149 through 191705-116 (Box 271)
    - Docket Range 191705-117 through 191706-68 (Box 272)
    - Docket Range 191706-69 through 191707-53 (Box 273)
    - Docket Range 191707-54 through 191708-41 (Box 274)
    - Docket Range 191708-42 through 191709-33 (Box 275)
    - Docket Range 191709-34 through 191710-74 (Box 276)
    - Docket Range 191710-74 through 191711-25 (Box 277)
    - Docket Range 191711-26 through 191712-75 (Box 278)
    - Docket Range 191712-76 through 191801-100 (Box 279)
    - Docket Range 191801-101 through 191802-30 (Box 280)
    - Docket Range 191802-31 through 191803-40 (Box 281)
    - Docket Range 191803-41 through 191804-9 (Box 282)
    - Docket Range 191804-10 through 191804-286 (Box 283)
    - Docket Range 191804-287 through 191805-290 (Box 284)
    - Docket Range 191805-291 through 191806-269 (Box 285)
    - Docket Range 191806-270 through 191807-199 (Box 286)
    - Docket Range 191807-200 through 191808-244 (Box 287)
    - Docket Range 191808-245 through 191809-223 (Box 288)
    - Docket Range 191809-224 through 191810-308 (Box 289)
    - Docket Range 191810-309 through 191811-154 (Box 290)
    - Docket Range 191811-155 through 191811-440 (Box 291)
    - Docket Range 191811-441 through 191812-296 (Box 292)
    - Docket Range 191812-297 through 191901-237 (Box 293)
    - Docket Range 191901-238 through 191902-230 (Box 294)
    - Docket Range 191902-231 through 191903-210 (Box 295)
    - Docket Range 191903-211 through 191904-180 (Box 296)
    - Docket Range 191904-181 through 191905-156 (Box 297)
    - Docket Range 191905-157 through 191906-156 (Box 298)
    - Docket Range 191906-157 through 191907-157 (Box 299)
    - Docket Range 191907-158 through 191909-40 (Box 300)
    - Docket Range 191909-40 through 191909-254 (Box 301)
    - Docket Range 191910-1 through 191911-66 (Box 302)
    - Docket Range 191911-67 through 191912-145 (Box 303)
    - Docket Range 191912-146 through 192001-145 (Box 304)
    - Docket Range 192001-146 through 192002-197 (Box 305)
    - Docket Range 192002-198 through 192003-180 (Box 306)
    - Docket Range 192003-181 through 192004-221 (Box 307)
    - Docket Range 192004-222 through 192006-115 (Box 308)
    - Docket Range 192006-116 through 192007-174 (Box 309)
    - Docket Range 192007-175 through 192009-42 (Box 310)
    - Docket Range 192009-43 through 192010-80 (Box 311)
    - Docket Range 192010-81 through 192011-135 (Box 312)
    - Docket Range 192011-136 through 192101-38 (Box 313)
    - Docket Range 192101-39 through 192102-80 (Box 314)
    - Docket Range 192102-81 through 192103-130 (Box 315)
    - Docket Range 192103-131 through 192104-188 (Box 316)
    - Docket Range 192104-189 through 1921106-40 (Box 317)
    - Docket Range 192106-41 through 192107-76 (Box 318)
    - Docket Range 192107-77 through 192108-130 (Box 319)
    - Docket Range 192108-131 through 192109-195 (Box 320)
    - Docket Range 192109-196 through 192111-54 (Box 321)
    - Docket Range 192111-55 through 192112-161 (Box 322)
    - Docket Range 192112-162 through 192201-220 (Box 323)
    - Docket Range 192201-221 through 192202-218 (Box 324)
    - Docket Range 192202-219 through 192204-55 (Box 325)
    - Docket Range 192204-56 through 192205-133 (Box 326)
    - Docket Range 192205-134 through 192206-154 (Box 327)